Privacy Policy

|     |
| --- |
| 2016<br><br>**2007 - 2009**<br><br>**What information do we collect?**  <br>  <br>We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.  <br>  <br>When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  <br>  <br>**What do we use your information for?**  <br>  <br>Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  <br>  <br>; To process transactions  <br><br>> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.<br><br>  <br>; To send periodic emails  <br>  <br>The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  <br>  <br>**How do we protect your information?**  <br>  <br>We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.  <br>  <br>After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.  <br>  <br>**Do we use cookies?**  <br>  <br>Many websites, such as news sites and blogs, partner with Google to  <br>show ads to their visitors. Working with Google partners, Google may use  <br>cookies for a number of purposes, such as to stop you seeing the same ad  <br>over and over again, to detect and stop click fraud, and to show ads that  <br>are likely to be more relevant  <br>(such as ads based on websites you have visited).  <br>  <br>**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  <br>  <br>We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  <br>  <br>**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  <br>  <br>We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  <br>  <br>**Terms and Conditions**  <br>  <br>Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.maryfi.com/](https://www.maryfi.com/)  <br>  <br>**Your Consent**  <br>  <br>By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).  <br>  <br>**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  <br>  <br>If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  <br>  <br>This policy was last modified on 2014  <br>  <br>**Contacting Us**  <br>  <br>If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  <br>  <br><br>### How you can control advertising cookies<br><br>You can use [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/?hl=en) to manage the Google ads you see.<br><br>You can also manage many companies� cookies used for online advertising at the US-based [aboutads.info choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) page or the EU-based[Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices).<br><br>Finally, you can [manage cookies in your web browser](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/managing/).<br><br>Other technologies used in advertising<br>--------------------------------------<br><br>Google�s advertising systems may use other technologies, including Flash and HTML5, for functions like display of interactive ad formats. We may use the [IP address](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/key-terms/#toc-terms-ip), for example, to identify your general location. We may also select advertising based on information about your computer or device, such as your device model, browser type, or sensors in your device like the accelerometer.<br><br>  <br>  <br>[http://www.maryfi.com/](https://www.maryfi.com/ "MaryFi.com")  <br>kw  <br>ahmadi, kw  <br>WApp: +965-66259509  <br>kuwait  <br>[\[email protected\]](https://www.maryfi.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  <br>  <br><br>**Privacy Policy [maryfi.com](https://www.maryfi.com/).**<br><br>**2016**<br><br> **Privacy Policy for** [MaryFi.com/](https://www.maryfi.com/) |
| في [MaryF.com](https://www.maryfi.com/) ، خصوصية زوارنا لها أهمية بالغة بالنسبة لنا. سياسة الخصوصية الموجودة في هذه الوثيقة تمثل الخطوط العريضة لأنواع المعلومات الشخصية التي نجمعها وكيفية استخدامها من قبلنا ومن قبل معلنينا .<br><br>* نحن في [MaryF.com](https://www.maryfi.com/) نستخدم إعلانات Google، بصفتها مورِّدًا مالياً خارجيًا، ولذلك تستخدم شركة جوجل [ملفات تعريف الارتباطات](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) لعرض الإعلانات على موقعنا.<br>* وبذلك ستتمكّن Google، باستخدام ملف تعريف الارتباط DART، من عرض الإعلانات "حسب الإهتمامات" للمستخدمين إستنادًا إلى زياراتهم لموقعنا و المدونة و المنتدى.<br>* و بالتأكيد زوارنا الكرام يمكنهم  تعطيل إستخدام ملف تعريف الارتباط DART بزيارة [سياسة الخصوصية الخاصة بإعلانات Google و شبكة المحتوى](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).<br><br>**ملفات الدخول:**  <br>نعم مثل معظم خوادم المواقع الأخرى ، ومن هنا فإن [MaryF.com](https://www.maryfi.com/) يستخدم نظام ملفات الدخول. و هذا يشمل كمثال بروتوكول الانترنت (عناوين ، نوع المتصفح ، مزود خدمة الانترنت (مقدمي خدمات الانترنت) ،  التاريخ / الوقت ، وعدد النقرات لتحليل الإتجاهات).<br><br>من خلال هذه العملية  لا يقصد جمع هذه المعلومات في سبيل التلصص على أمور الزوار الشخصية ، وإنما هي أمور تحليلية لأغراض تحسين جودة الإعلانات من قبلGoogle ، ويضاف إلى ذلك أن جميع هذه المعلومات المحفوظة من قبلنا سرية تماما، وتبقى ضمن نطاق التطوير والتحسين الخاص بموقعنا فقط و لن تباع أو تشارك مع طرف ثالث.  <br>  <br>**الكوكيز وإعدادات الشبكة:**  <br>إن شركة Google تستخدم تقنية الكوكيز لتخزين المعلومات الخاصة باهتمامات الزوار، إلى جانب سجل خاص للمستخدم تسجل فيه معلومات محددة عن الصفحات التي تم الوصول إليها أو زيارتها، وبهذه الخطوة فإننا نعرف مدى اهتمامات الزوار و أي المواضيع الأكثر تفضيلاً من قبلهم حتى نستطيع من جانبنا تطوير محتوانا الخدمي و المعرفي المناسب لهم.   <br>  <br>نضيف إلى ذلك أن بعض الشركات التي تعلن في موقعنا قد و لكن ليس بالضرورة تطلع على الكوكيز و إعدادات الشبكة الخاصة بموقعنا و بكم، و من هذه الشركات على سبيل المثال لا الحصر شركة [Google](https://www.google.com/) و برنامجها الإعلاني [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/login/en_US/?hl=en_US&sourceid=aso&subid=ww-en_US-et-ads&medium=link&gsessionid=rZcHLpemZWE) و هي شركة الإعلانات الأولى في موقعنا .  <br>  <br>مثل هذه الشركات المعلنة و التي تعتبر الطرف الثالث في سياسة الخصوصية تتابع هذه البيانات والإحصائيات عبر بروتوكولات الإنترنت لأغراض تحسين جودة إعلاناتها و قياس مدى فعاليتها. كما و إن هذه الشركات و بموجب الإتفاقيات المبرمة معنا يحق لها استخدام وسائل تقنية مثل ( الكوكيز، إعدادات الشبكة، وأكواد برمجية خاصة "جافا سكربت" ) لنفس الأغراض المذكورة أعلاه و التي تتلخص في تطوير المحتوى الإعلاني لهذه الشركات و قياس مدى فاعلية هذه الإعلانات ، من دون أي أهداف أخرى قد تضر بشكل أو بآخر زوار موقعنا.  <br>   <br>إن [MaryF.com](https://www.maryfi.com/)  لا يستطيع الوصول أو السيطرة على هذه الملفات، و حتى بعد سماحك وتفعيلك لأخذها من جهازك (الكوكيز) ، كما و نعتبر أنفسنا غير مسؤولين بأي شكل من الأشكال عن الاستخدام غير المصرح به إن حصل  .   <br>  <br>عليك مراجعة سياسة الخصوصية الخاصة بالطرف الثالث في هذه الوثيقة (الشركات المعلنة "[Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/login/en_US/?hl=en_US&sourceid=aso&subid=ww-en_US-et-ads&medium=link&gsessionid=rZcHLpemZWE)" ) أو خوادم الشبكات الإعلانية لمزيد من المعلومات عن ممارساتها و أنشطتها المختلفة .  <br>  <br>لمراجعة سياسة الخصوصية للبرنامج الإعلاني الأول [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/login/en_US/?hl=en_US&sourceid=aso&subid=ww-en_US-et-ads&medium=link&gsessionid=rZcHLpemZWE) والتابع لشركة [Google](https://www.google.com/) يرجى النقر [هنا](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  <br>   <br>وأخيرا .. نحن ملزمون ضمن بنود هذه الاتفاقية بان نبين لك كيفية تعطيل خاصية الكوكيز، حيث يمكنك فعل ذلك من خلال خيارات المتصفح الخاص بك، أو من خلال متابعة  [سياسة الخصوصية الخاصة بإعلانات Google وشبكة المحتوى](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) .   <br>   <br>  <br>إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي مزيد من **المعلومات** أو لديك أية **أسئلة** عن **سياسة الخصوصية** ، لا تتردد [بالاتصال بنا](https://www.maryfi.com/contact.php)<br><br>بنود هذه السياسة قابلة للتطوير والتغيير في محتواها في أي وقت نراه ضرورياً |
